Guide to the Artists Space Collection of Artist Files MSS.506
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Thomas, Francois, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 85)
- Thomas, Kathleen, 1976-2003 (Box 54, Folder 86)
- Thomas, Nadine, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 87)
- Thomas, Richard, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 88)
- Thomas, Robyn, 2002-2004 (Box 54, Folder 89)
- Thomas, Robyn J., 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 81)
- Thompson, Jabouloni, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 82)
- Thompson, Mark, 1997-2004 (Box 54, Folder 83)
- Thompson, Jr., Art, 1989-2005 (Box 54, Folder 84)
- Thomsen, Tamara, 2000-2003 (Box 54, Folder 90)
- Thorsen, Niels, 2000-2002 (Box 54, Folder 91)
- Thulen, Tom, 1993-1999 (Box 54, Folder 92)
- Thurston, Jonathan, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Thyzel, Tim, 1992-2000 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Tice, Michael, 1984-1997 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Tichane, Robin, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Tijnagel, Arno, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Tileston, Jackie, 1999-2001 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Tilly, Herbert, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Timberlake, Emily, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Timm, Kate, 1993-2005 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Timms, Cynthia, 1993-2003 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Tirr, Catherine, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Tiscareno, Bedel, 2001-2002 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Tiso, Barbara, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Tobias, Rosalind, 1995-1997 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Toda, Fumiko, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Todd, Patrick, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Tohara, Kaoru, 1991-2002 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Tokmakov, Larissa, 1995-2000 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Tolan, Fran, 1999-2002 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Tolbert, Jeffrey, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Tomaino, Leah, 1996-2001 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Tomczyk, Joanna W., 2004 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Tomei, Romeo/Robert, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Tondrick, Lynn, 1993-1997 (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Tonetti, Joe, 2002-2005 (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Tong, Diane, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Tong, Jessie, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 34)
- Topete, Luna, 2001-2004 (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Torano, Vince, 1994-2001 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Torpey, Eileen, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 29)
- Torres, Marisa, 2000-2001 (Box 55, Folder 30)
- Toshida, Mitsuo, 1988-2001 (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Touby, Linda, 1992-2001 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Towery, Terry, 1998-2002 (Box 55, Folder 32)
- Towne, George, 1997-2001 (Box 55, Folder 33)
- Townsend, Jamie, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 34)
- Traasdahl, Per, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 35)
- Tracy, Jay B., 1996-2005 (Box 55, Folder 36)
- Tran, Hong, 2003-2004 (Box 55, Folder 38)
- Trautwein, Jurgen, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 37)
- Travanti, Marc, 1990-1994 (Box 55, Folder 40)
- Tredway, Tony, 1998-2001 (Box 55, Folder 41)
- Treinen, Suzanne, 1994-1998 (Box 55, Folder 42)
- Trent, Gilbert, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 43)
- Trento, Giovanna, 1992-1994 (Box 55, Folder 44)
- Trese, Daniel, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 45)
- Trevino, Louis Vega, 1995-2001 (Box 55, Folder 46)
- Trigg, Sarah, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 47)
- Trillo, Charo, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 48)
- Tringas, Kallerroy, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 49)
- Triplett, Ginna, 2002-2003 (Box 55, Folder 50)
- Trojan, Stefanie, 2003-2004 (Box 55, Folder 51)
- Troy, Priscilla, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 53)
- Troy, Suzannah B., 1996-1998 (Box 55, Folder 52)
- Trzebinski, Gabriela, 2001-2003 (Box 55, Folder 54)
- Tsai, Shu-Hui, 1992-1997 (Box 66, Folder 35)
- Tsai, Yeachin, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 55)
- Tsao, Richard, 1986-2001 (Box 55, Folder 56)
- Tsay, Chwen Wen, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 57)
- Tschampel, Nicole, 1999-2004 (Box 55, Folder 58)
- Tsers, Andrey, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 59)
- Tsesarskaya, Marina, 1999-2000 (Box 55, Folder 60)
- Tsong, Jane, 1997-2001 (Box 66, Folder 36)
- Tsukamoto, Yasuko, 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 61)
- Tucker, Brynna, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 62)
- Tucker, Mindy, 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 63)
- Tullius, Traci, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 64)
- Tuminello, Sara, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 65)
- Tuncer, Levent, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 62)
- Tung, Eugenie, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 66)
- Tunner, Angela, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 67)
- Turczyn, Pamela, 1986-1989 (Box 55, Folder 68)
- Turkell, Michael Harlan, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 69)
- Turley, Shelley, 1998-2001 (Box 55, Folder 70)
- Tursini, Vanna, 2000-2001 (Box 55, Folder 71)
- Turtel, Joel, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 72)
- Tushev, Georgi, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 73)
- Tweed, Heather, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 74)
- Twomey, Chris, 1999-2005 (Box 55, Folder 75)
- Tyler, Jo, 1999-2000 (Box 55, Folder 76)
- Tyler, Mark, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 77)
- Uchida, Ritsko, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 37)
- Ueda, Kako, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 78)
- Ueda, Kenji, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 80)
- Uehling, Judith, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 79)
- Uekawa, Aya, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 81)
- Ukaji, Kaori, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 82)
- Ullmann, Jim, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 100)
- Ulrich, Courtney, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 83)
- Ulrich, Don, 1997-2001 (Box 55, Folder 84)
- Umehara, Yoko, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Umlauf, Lynn, 1992-2000 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Umlauf, Madelon, 1995-2001 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Ungar, Joanne, 1999-2003 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Unger, Adele, 1990-1995 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- United Graffiti Artists, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Unknown Artist, undated (Box 66, Folder 57)
- Unrein, Suzanne, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Unruh, Jennifer, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Urban, Jason, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Urban, Tao, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 59)
- Urkowitz, Rachel, 1999-2002 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Urso, Josette, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Usui, Takashi, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Uterberg, Charles, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Vadera, Jaret, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Vag, Anna-Mana, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Vaia, Antonietta, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Vaida, Jonas, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Valentino, Michael, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Valla, Teressa, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Valu, Pascal, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Van Anden, Jason, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Van Cura, Marjorie, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Van de Bovenkamp, Hans, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 54)
- van de Kreeke, Peter Anthonie, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Van Dyke, Aaron, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Van Dyke, Denise, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 30)
- Van Fleet, Janet, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 32)
- Van Houten, Lori, 2001-2005 (Box 56, Folder 33)
- van Hulsteyn, Debra, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Van Leeuwen, Gerda, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 34)
- van Lingen, Claude, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 35)
- Van Meeuwen, Hans, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 36)
- Vandenburgh, Laura, 1998-2005 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Vander Meer, Kerry, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Vanderkaay, Cody, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Vanderveen, Kimetha, 2001-2002 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- VanGorder, Edwin "Van", 2001 (Box 66, Folder 43)
- Vapnek, Susanna, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 38)
- Vargas, Claudia, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 37)
- Varnot, Annie, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 39)
- Vasin, Ted, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 40)
- Vavakova, Ivana, 1993-2000 (Box 56, Folder 42)
- Vaynshteyn, Aleksey, 2001-2003 (Box 56, Folder 41)
- Vega, Thomas, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 43)
- Venegas, Evan, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 44)
- Venske and Spanle, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 45)
- Veraldi, Anne, 1986-2001 (Box 56, Folder 46)
- Vercauteren, Vick, 1999-2000 (Box 66, Folder 38)
- Verrechia, Jean, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 47)
- Verzi, Edgardo, 1997-2001 (Box 56, Folder 48)
- Vesselovskaya, Natalia, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 49)
- Viale, Susanna, undated (Box 64, Folder 82)
- Vialu, Carlo, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 50)
- Vickers, Marques, 2000-2001 (Box 56, Folder 51)
- Vidal, Ferran, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 52)
- Vidal, Francisco, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 53)
- Vieira, Claudia, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 54)
- Vielhaben, Ines, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 55)
- Viera, Conny, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 53)
- Vigliani, Sylvia, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 56)
- Vigon, David, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 57)
- Vilarrasa, Ana, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 59)
- Villalba, Jovan, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 60)
- Villanes, Eduardo, 1998-2004 (Box 56, Folder 61)
- Villanueva, Fred, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 62)
- Villareal, Jean-Claude, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 63)
- Villasmil, Alejandra, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 64)
- Villaverde Cabral, Joana, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 65)
- Villiger, Judit, 2000-2002 (Box 66, Folder 52)
- Villotaf, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 78)
- Vinas, Jose Luis, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 66)
- Vine, Marlene, 1994-2001 (Box 56, Folder 67)
- Vine, Rachel, 2001-2002 (Box 56, Folder 68)
- Vineta, Kaulaca, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 69)
- Viola, Jennifer, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 70)
- Virgien, David, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 51)
- Vishlitzky, Tamar, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 71)
- Vita, Grazia, 2000-2001 (Box 56, Folder 72)
- Vitale, Robert, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 58)
- Vitali, Julius, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 50)
- Vitamvas, Gretchen, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 73)
- Viveiros, Kazaan, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 74)
- Vladulescu, Nick D., 2002 (Box 56, Folder 75)
- Voelker, Roger, 1996-1997 (Box 56, Folder 76)
- Voerman, Rob, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 77)
- Vogel, Virginia, 1994-2001 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Vogwill, Sarah, 2000-2002 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Voisey, Gordon, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 39)
- Volk, Karl, 1998-1999 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Vollmer, April, 1996-2001 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Volo, Alfonso, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Von Der Heydt, Hardey, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Von Ehr, Anne, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Von Ha, Gustavo, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- von Krahe, Helmut, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- von Mallinckrodt, Mumm, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Von-Mertens, Anna, 1999-2003 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Vossoughi, Anahita, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Vuillaume, Jean Pierre, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Vurgaropulou, Fotini, 1998-2002 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Wachter, Carolann, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Wadsworth, Susan, 1990-2001 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Waegner, Uta, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Waguri, Reiko, 1992-2001 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Wahl, Jonathan, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Wahlah, Naseem, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Wain, Erika, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Waligore, Athena, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Walker, Andrew, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Walker, Katie, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Walker, Lois, 1978-2001 (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Meli Walker, Nancy, 1986-1991 (Box 57, Folder 27)
- Walker-Fields, Pat, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Wallenberg-Olsson, Paulina, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Wallis, Scott, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Wallower, Nora, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 40)
- Walsh, Frank, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 30)
- Walters, Suzanne, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 31)
- Wandell, Annie, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 32)
- Warden, Oliver, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 33)
- Wardle, Darren, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 34)
- Warner, Jessica, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 35)
- Warren, Lisa, 1994-2002 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Warshauer, Sheri, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 36)
- Was, Lauren, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 37)
- Wasilausky, Sara, 1999-2001 (Box 57, Folder 38)
- Wasko-Flood, Sandra, 1994-2001 (Box 57, Folder 39)
- Wasserman, Deborah, 1997-2000 (Box 57, Folder 40)
- Wasserman, Marcy, 1994-1999 (Box 57, Folder 42)
- Wasserman, Rebecca, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 41)
- Watanabe, Godai, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 41)
- Watanabe, Micki, 1992-2002 (Box 57, Folder 43)
- Watanabe, Nana, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 44)
- Watanabe, Tetsu, 1984-1997 (Box 57, Folder 45)
- Waterman, Jill, 1984-2001 (Box 57, Folder 48)
- Waters, Claudia, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 46)
- Watkins, Allison, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 47)
- Watkins-Hughes, Ryan, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 49)
- Watlington, Robert, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 50)
- Watson, Claire, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Watson, Jennifer, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 51)
- Watson, Susan, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 52)
- Watts, Margaret, 2002-2003 (Box 57, Folder 53)
- Wayne, Brian, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 54)
- Weathersby, Ann, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 55)
- Weathersby, Ken, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 56)
- Weaver, W.W., 2003 (Box 57, Folder 57)
- Webb, Patrick, 1990-2001 (Box 57, Folder 58)
- Weber, David, 1994-2002 (Box 57, Folder 59)
- Weber, Matthew, 2001-2003 (Box 57, Folder 60)
- Webster, Frank, 1997-2005 (Box 57, Folder 61)
- Weedman, Russell, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 62)
- Weglarz, Lorraine, 2000-2005 (Box 57, Folder 63)
- Wegman, Laura Jo, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 64)
- Wehner, Rainer Maria, 1996-1998 (Box 57, Folder 65)
- Weidkam, Rachel, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 66)
- Weileder, Wolfgang, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 67)
- Weinberg, Louise, 1990-2001 (Box 57, Folder 68)
- Weinmann, Bert, 1986-1988 (Box 57, Folder 69)
- Weinstock, Rose, 1999-2001 (Box 57, Folder 70)
- Weis, Betsy, 1991-2003 (Box 57, Folder 71)
- Weiss, Dina, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 72)
- Weiss, Josh, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 73)
- Weiss, Lawrence, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Weissberger, Barbara, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Weissglass, Jeannie, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Wellens, Debra, 1989-2001 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Wells, Ciera C., 2001 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Wels, D., 1990-2001 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Werner, Michael, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Werth, Andrew, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Weseley, Matthew, 1983-2003 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- West, Anna, 1993-1999 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- West, Christina, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Westerfield, Bob, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Westheimer, Bill, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Westheimer and Schwartz, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Westmore, Evi, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Wexler, Aaron, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Wexler, Brett, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Whalen, Benji, 1998-2002 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Wheatley, Charmaine, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 49)
- whilden, Jojo, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Whitaker, Corinne, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- White, Ian, 1984-1989 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- White, Keith, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 22)
- White, Lili, 2000-2002 (Box 58, Folder 23)
- White, Roger, 1988-2001 (Box 58, Folder 24)
- White, Susan, 2000-2002 (Box 58, Folder 25)
- White, Wendy, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Whitman, Phillip, 2004-2005 (Box 58, Folder 27)
- Widelitz, Jody, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Wiener, Deborah, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 30)
- Wiese, Allison, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Wiesenberg, Harvey, 1990-1999 (Box 58, Folder 32)
- Wiggins, Cynthia, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 33)
- Wight, Sara, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Wilke, Stefan, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 35)
- Wilkin, Charles, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 34)
- Wilks, Harry, 1979-2001 (Box 58, Folder 36)
- Willey, Brian, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 37)
- William, David, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 38)
- Williams, Harry, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 39)
- Williams, Idaherma, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 40)
- Williams, James, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 41)
- Williams, Jeffrey, 1994-1999 (Box 58, Folder 43)
- Williams, Mark, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 42)
- Williams, Mark, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 46)
- Williams, Rosemary, 2002-2004 (Box 58, Folder 50)
- Williams, Wendy Ide, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 44)
- Williamson, Kathryn, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 45)
- Willis, Corey, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 47)
- Wills, Miriam, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 48)
- Wilschut, Hans, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 83)
- Wilson, Kristiina, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 49)
- Wilson, Letha, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 51)
- Wilson, Nancy, 1995-1996 (Box 58, Folder 52)
- Wilson, Olivia B., 1988-1995 (Box 58, Folder 53)
- Wilson, Stewart, 1986-1989 (Box 58, Folder 54)
- Wilson, Timothy, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 55)
- Winget-Gibson, Jean A., 2003 (Box 58, Folder 56)
- Winika, Cynthia, 1998-2001 (Box 58, Folder 58)
- Winkler, Andrea, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 57)
- Winkler, Mary Jane, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 59)
- Winograde, Edie, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 60)
- Winshtein, Paz, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 61)
- Without Canvas, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 62)
- Witteveen, Bettina, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 63)
- Witzich, Silke, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 64)
- Wodarek, James, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 65)
- Wofsey, Tammy, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 66)
- Wojahn, Mark, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 67)
- Wojtasik, Pawel, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 68)
- Wolanczyk, Roxanne, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 74)
- Wolf, Jeffrey, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 69)
- Wolf, Melissa, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 70)
- Wolf, Silvio, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 71)
- Wolff, Denise, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 72)
- Wolinska, Nadia, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 73)
- Wolkoff, Katherine, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 75)
- Wollmam, Nan, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 76)
- Wolowski, Edward, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Won, Hae-Won, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Wong, Holly, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Wong, Katarina, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Wong, Sandra, 1994-2001 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Wong, Yuh-Shioh, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Wood, Deanna, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Wood, Meghan, 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Wood, Mia, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Wood, Robert, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Wood, Stefan, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Woodeson, Ben, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Woods, Rebecca, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Wooh, Suhee, 2000-2005 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Woolcock-Schwartz, Jennifer, 1999-2002 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Wooten, Benjamin, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Workman, Cindy, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Wray, Randy, 1998-2001 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Wrenn C., Scrapworm, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Wright, Jay, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Wright, Robert, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Wright, Sofia, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Wroblewski, Jennifer, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Wu, Jun, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Wu, Moonching, 2000-2003 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Wu, Peter, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Wurm, Jan, 2000-2004 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Wurm, Jason John, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Wurtzel, Daniel, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Wyffels, David, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Wyllie, Nancy E., 2002-2005 (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Wynne, Richard, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 32)
- Wynveld, Barbara, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Wyss, Laura, 1992-1999 (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Xavier, Ricardo, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Xi, Leif Inge, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Yadzinski, Stephen, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 36)
- Yakushiji, Key, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 37)
- Yamada-Fernandez, Junko, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 38)
- Yamaguchi, Riichi, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 39)
- Yamaguchi, Yuriko, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 40)
- Yamamoto, Lynn, 1990-1993 (Box 66, Folder 42)
- Yamamoto, Taka, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 41)
- Yamazaki, Masami, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 42)
- Yanes, Jacob, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 43)
- Yaneta, Jaanise, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 44)
- Yang, Haeyoung, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 45)
- Yang, Hee Sung, 2001-2004 (Box 59, Folder 46)
- Yang, Laura, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 47)
- Yankowitz, Nina, 1982-1996 (Box 59, Folder 48)
- Yassin, Aaron, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 49)
- Yates, Allen, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 50)
- Yates, Alec, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 51)
- Yawney, Max, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 52)
- Yeh, C.J., 2002 (Box 59, Folder 53)
- Yepoyan, Armen, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 47)
- Yeomans, Erika, 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 54)
- Yockel, Justin, 1998-2001 (Box 59, Folder 55)
- Yoda, Yoichiro, 1995-2000 (Box 59, Folder 56)
- Yoder, Charles, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 57)
- Yokomizo, Miyuki, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 58)
- Yoo, Hye-Jin, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 59)
- Yoo, Sun Choi, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 46)
- Yoon, Heeseop, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 60)
- Yoon, Maria, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 61)
- Yoon, Mia, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 62)
- Yoon, Sunlee, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 45)
- Yoon, Youngcheol, 1999-2001 (Box 66, Folder 60)
- Yordanov, Plamen, 1992-2000 (Box 59, Folder 63)
- Yoshimizu, Hiroshi, 1999-2001 (Box 59, Folder 64)
- Yosten, Laura, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 65)
- Youens, Rachel, 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 66)
- Young, Alex, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 68)
- Young, Laura, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 67)
- Young, Lisa, 2003-2005 (Box 59, Folder 69)
- Young, Lynus, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 70)
- Young, Millicent, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 71)
- Young, Shane, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 72)
- Young Sun, Lim, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 73)
- Yourdon, Patrice, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 74)
- Yousefian, Shadi, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 75)
- Yu, Jihyun, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 44)
- Yuan, Seldon, 2003-2005 (Box 59, Folder 76)
- Yuen, Allen, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 77)
- Yun, Cheryl, 2002-2003 (Box 59, Folder 78)
- Yung, Susan, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 79)
- Zabala, Eduardo, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Zacharias, Athos, 2001-2006 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Zacharow, Christopher M., 1998-2002 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Zachary, Michael, 2004-2006 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Zackin, Jennifer, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Zafar, Omar, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Zahn, Marilu, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Zaitsev, George, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Zajac, Ron, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Zalk, Jason, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Zanelli, Barbara, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Zanisnik, Bryan, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Zanni, Carlo, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Zapfel, Kurt, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Zarate, Patricia, 2001-2003 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Zarzeczna, Monika, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Zawada, Elizabeth, 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Zawadzka, Iwona, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Zehngut, William, 2002-2003 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Zeller, Robert, 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Zevin, Alexandra, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Zexter, Melissa, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Zghal, Emna, 2001-2002 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Zhang, O, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Zhao, Suikang, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Zick, Carolyn, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- Zighelboim, Ivette, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Zigova, Anabela, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Zimmerman, Aaron, 2001-2003 (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Zimmermann, Andy, 1996-1998 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Zinn, Rob, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Zinnes, Alice, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- Ziperstein, Bari, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 32)
- Zizioli, Chiara, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 33)
- Zlotsky, Deborah, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 34)
- Zobova, Marina, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- Zoller, John, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 36)
- Zollinger, Raphael, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 37)
- Zopp, Dudley, 1998-2002 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- Zweibel, Jane, 1990-1998 (Box 66, Folder 55)
- Zweig, Ellen, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 56)
- Zweig, Janet, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 39)
- Zwerling, Lisa, 1993-2001 (Box 60, Folder 40)
- Zwibel, Helaine, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 41)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 67)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 68)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 69)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 70)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 71)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 72)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 73)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 74)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 75)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 76)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 77)
- Digital Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 78, Box Shared Fales 082, Box Shared Fales 083, Box Shared Fales 036)
- Audiovisual Separations, 1972-2009 (Box 79)